<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:ror="http://rorweb.com/0.1/">
    <channel>
        <title>ROR Sitemap for https://www.fairmountvagamon.com/</title>
        <link>https://www.fairmountvagamon.com/</link>

        <item>
            <link>https://fairmountvagamon.com/</link>
            <title>Welcome to Fairmount Resorts Vagamon, Kerala - Discover the Idyllic Beauty of Vagamon at Fairmount</title>
            <description>Escape to the stunning beauty of Vagamon at Fairmount Resorts. Our resort
                offers comfortable accommodations, a range of dining options, and a range of
                activities and amenities to ensure that our guests have a comfortable and enjoyable
                stay. Address: Fairmount Vagamon Kannamkulam, Vagamon Kerala - 685503 Contact: +91
                88488 86990</description>
            <ror:type>Main</ror:type>
            <ror:image>https://www.fairmountvagamon.com/logo.png</ror:image>
            <ror:updatePeriod>day</ror:updatePeriod>
            <ror:sortOrder>0</ror:sortOrder>
        </item>
        <item>
            <link>https://fairmountvagamon.com/rooms</link>
            <title>Fairmount Resorts - Experience the Best of Vagamon in Our Exquisite Rooms</title>
            <description>Discover the true essence of Vagamon at Fairmount Resorts. Our exquisite
                rooms offer the perfect blend of modern amenities and traditional charm, making it
                the ideal base for exploring the natural beauty and cultural treasures of Vagamon.
                Book your stay now to experience the best of Vagamon.</description>
            <ror:type>Rooms</ror:type>
            <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
        </item>
        <item>
            <link>https://fairmountvagamon.com/experiences</link>
            <title>Fairmount Experiences - Explore the Natural Beauty and Cultural Treasures of
                Vagamon</title>
            <description>Experience the beauty and rich cultural heritage of Vagamon at Fairmount
                Resorts. Explore the natural landscapes and cultural treasures of this picturesque
                destination, with exquisite accommodation and blissful experiences. Book your stay
                now and discover the magic of Vagamon.</description>
            <ror:type>Experiences</ror:type>
            <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
        </item>
        <item>
            <link>https://fairmountvagamon.com/gallery</link>
            <title>Fairmount Gallery - A Picture is worth a Thousand Words, See the Beauty of
                Vagamon through our Gallery</title>
            <description>Explore the idyllic views of Vagamon at Fairmount Resorts. Our photo
                gallery captures the natural beauty of the region, from lush hills to tranquil
                lakes. Book your stay now and experience the enchanting beauty of Vagamon for
                yourself.</description>
            <ror:type>Gallery</ror:type>
            <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
        </item>
        <item>
            <link>https://fairmountvagamon.com/contact</link>
            <title>Fairmount Resorts</title>
            <description>Escape to the stunning beauty of Vagamon at Fairmount Residency. Our resort
                offers comfortable accommodations, a range of dining options, and a range of
                activities and amenities to ensure that our guests have a comfortable and enjoyable
                stay.</description>
            <ror:type>Contact</ror:type>
            <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
        </item>
        <item>
            <link>https://fairmountvagamon.com/book</link>
            <title>Fairmount Resorts - Book your Stay to Experience the Enchanting Beauty of Vagamon</title>
            <description>Discover the natural splendor of Vagamon at Fairmount Resorts. Our
                well-appointed rooms and unparalleled experiences will make your stay unforgettable.
                Book now to experience the enchanting beauty of Vagamon.</description>
            <ror:type>Book</ror:type>
            <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
        </item>
        <item>
            <link>https://fairmountvagamon.com/faq</link>
            <title>Fairmount Resorts - FAQ </title>
            <description>Fairmount Resorts - Frequently Asked Questions</description>
            <ror:type>FAQ</ror:type>
            <ror:sortOrder>1</ror:sortOrder>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sitemap</title>
            <ror:type>Sitemap</ror:type>
            <ror:seeAlso>https://fairmountvagamon.com/sitemap.xml</ror:seeAlso>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
  